

# CONTACT

#### **Phone**

012 - 898 1055

#### **Email**

xianzyip8@gmail.com

#### **Address**

46, Tingkat Bunga Raya, Taman On, 31650 Ipoh, Perak.

# SKILLS

- Swift
- Java
- Kotlin
- C#
- Tailwind
- Unity
- WordPress R Programming
- TypeScript PHP/SQL
- React.js
- Next.js
- Three.js
- Web Development

# REFERENCES

#### Mr. Amad Arshad

Senior Lecturer, Faculty of Computing

**Phone:** 019 - 303 6135

Email: amad.arshad@apu.edu.my

#### Ms. Abbhirami Sivarajan

Lecturer, Faculty of Business

**Phone:** 017 - 648 5551

Email: abbhirami@apu.edu.my

# CO-CURRICULUM

President of Sam Tet Archery Club (2018/19)

Secretary of Sam Tet Math Club (2017/19)

Red Stripe in Taekwondo Practice

Bassoonist in Kinta Valley Wind Orchestra and Sam Tet Symphony Orchestra

# Yip Zi Xian

Mobile Developer / Software Engineer

# **PROFILE INFO**

Continuously searching for experiences and improvements. Dedicated to work, love to be in a team, and work well under stress. Adaptive and likes to manage different tasks given according to priority. Willing to learn what I don't know, willing to teach what I know to who willing to learn. Achievement-affiliated in terms of coffee breaks.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Studio20 / The Techy Hub

Front-end Developer / Intern

May 2022 - Oct 2022

- Web development / Minor UI-UX practices
- Responsible for working on a single small project
- Co-operate in teams for large projects
- · Research on multiple JavaScript libraries and frameworks

## **Erican Language Centre**

Part-Timer

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

- Help in front-desk tasks
- Communicate with clients through physical meeting or phone.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Asia Pacific University**

BSc (Hons) in Information Technology (Mobile Technology) Nov 2022 - Present

• CGPA (First Semester): 3.72

Diploma in Software Engineering

May 2020 - May 2022

• CGPA (Total): 3.48

## **PROJECTS**

#### Chateau Du Nox

• A vineyard application developed using Swift along with CoreData, MapKit frameworks

#### **Speed Parcel**

• Object-oriented Delivery System in Java Swing for Admin and Public Users

ME-Website II

• Ongoing responsive portfolio website created using Vite, R3F, and TailwindCSS